Guide to the Elmer Holmes Bobst Collection MSS.067
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Awards, Plaques, Medals, Certificates and Honors.
  - Subseries A: Boxed Awards.
    - Speech Rehabilitation Institute. Awards Banquet in honor of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Program, 1970; MSS.067.cuid20287 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Lundbeck [Germany]. Congratulatory message from "the staff" on Elmer Homes Bobst's 90th birthday, 1974-12-16; MSS.067.cuid20288 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Paul, King of Greece. Award to Elmer Homes Bobst of the Cross the Brigadier Generals of the Order of the Phoenix, 1956; MSS.067.cuid20289 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Pan American Medical Association. Honorary Membership, 1976; MSS.067.cuid20290 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - World Medical Association. Award for outstanding service, undated; MSS.067.cuid20291 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Salvation Army Association, New Jersey. Life Membership, undated; MSS.067.cuid20292 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Salvation Army Leadership Award, 1971; MSS.067.cuid20293 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - New York Academy of Science Certificate of Fellowship., undated; MSS.067.cuid20294 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Medical Society of the District of Columbia. Health U.S.A. Awards. Banquet Program, 1960; MSS.067.cuid20295 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Columbia University College of Pharmacy. Henry Hurd Rusby Award Program, 1961; MSS.067.cuid20296 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Treasury Department. Minute Man Statue, 1955; MSS.067.cuid20297 (Box 26)
    - New Jersey Savings Bond Staff. Minute Man Statue. Given on Elmer Holmes Bobst's 90th birthday in recognition of service., undated; MSS.067.cuid20298 (Box 26)
    - Horatio Alger Award of Schools and Colleges Association, 1965; MSS.067.cuid20299 (Box 27)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Memorial Award, 1973; MSS.067.cuid20300 (Box 61)
    - Theodore Von Karmann Award Certificate, 1972; MSS.067.cuid20301 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Ambassador Award. 1951, MSS.067.cuid20307 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Lancaster, Pa. J.A. Businessman Award. 1974, MSS.067.cuid20306 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - American Cancer Society. Honorary Member, National Board. 1962, MSS.067.cuid20304 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Rider College, New Jersey. Honorary L.L.D. [2 certificates], undated; MSS.067.cuid20308 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - American Cancer Society Citation, 1971., MSS.067.cuid20313 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania State Pharmaceutical Examining Board. Registered Assistant Pharmacist Certificate, 1905; MSS.067.cuid20302 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Canadian Foundation for the Advancement of Pharmacy, 1960., MSS.067.cuid20314 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Hahneman Medical College and Hospital, Philadelphia, Pa. Award. 1970, MSS.067.cuid20305 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Treasury. [2 citations] 1943., MSS.067.cuid20312 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Treasury War Finance Committee, New Jersey. Certificates, 4th through 6th War Loan, 1944., MSS.067.cuid20309 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Treasury War Finance Committee. Certificate in recognition of distinguished records, War Loans 1 through 6. 1944, MSS.067.cuid20310 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - World War II Veteran Association. Advisory Member. 1944, MSS.067.cuid20311 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster Rotary Club. Pennsylvania Ambassador Award. 1951, MSS.067.cuid20315 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - American Cancer Society, New Jersey. Certificate of Merit, 1956; MSS.067.cuid20303 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster Rotary Club. Pennsylvania Ambassador Award, program., 1951 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - American Physicians Art Association. Special Award. 1965, MSS.067.cuid20316 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Mario Negri Institute Foundation. Certificate of Achievement. 1978 (See also: Folder 5)., MSS.067.cuid20317 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Papanicolaou Cancer Research Institute. Founders Certificate. 1977 (See also: Folder 5)., MSS.067.cuid20318 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - American Cancer Society Certificate, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Various medals: Mario Negri Institute Foundation, 1978; Papanicolauou Cancer Research Institute, 1977; Chung-Ang University, Seoul, Korea, 1978., 1977-1978; MSS.067.cuid20319 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Framed Awards on Display.
    - U.S. Treasury Award. War Finance Committee, Newark, N.J. Certificate of Merit for Patriotic Service. 1945, MSS.067.cuid20320
    - Red Cross of Greater New York. War Fund. Certificate of Honor. 1944, MSS.067.cuid20321 (Box 67)
    - Hahnemann Medical College, Philadelphia. Pa. Honorary Doctor of Science Degree. 1957, MSS.067.cuid20322 (Box 105)
    - New York City. John V. Lindsay, Mayor. Citation for Distinguished and Exceptonal Service., 1972; MSS.067.cuid20323 (Box 62)
    - New York City. Abraham D. Beame, Mayor. Certificate of Appreciation on his 90th Birthday. 1974, MSS.067.cuid20324 (Box 62)
    - Pennsylvania State Certificate of Registered Pharmacist., 1905; MSS.067.cuid20325 (Box 84)
    - U.S. War Production Board. Certificate in recognition of Elmer Holmes Bobst's contribution to the war effort, undated; MSS.067.cuid20326 (Box 66)
    - American Cancer Society. Special Citation for Elmer Holmes Bobst's vision in his reorganization of the Society and for his "spiritual and business leadership" in the affairs of the Society. 1959, MSS.067.cuid20327 (Box 70)
    - American Society of Contemporary Medicine and Surgery. Distinguished Service Award. 1972, MSS.067.cuid20328 (Box 69)
- Series IV: Articles, Press Releases, Speeches and Correspondence.
  Series IV contains articles and newspaper clippings by and about Bobst, plus personal, professional, and political correspondence.
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1921-1954. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1955-1956. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1957-1959. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1960-1966. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1967-1973. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Hoffman-LaRoche, 25th Anniversary Brochure. 1930 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Article: Elmer Bobst-Vitamin King, by Meador Wright. Monthly Magazine of the Oranges and Montclair. Apr. 1943 p.11. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Elmer Bobst Heads Warner, The Apothecary, Jan. 1946 p.1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst, The Warner Orbis, Jan. 1946 p.1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Elmer Bobst Started his Career in a Drugstore, National Association of Retail Druggists. Journal, Feb. 4, 1946. p.242., undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Medicine, Time, Apr. 26, 1946. p.76. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Life Begins at 60, Time, Feb. 11, 1952. p.38. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Men of Letters, Elmer H. Bobst, Better Impressions, 1st Quarter, 1952. p.8. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Merger-Minded Warner-Lambert, Fortune, Oct. 1955, p.43. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Elmer H. Bobst Lauded by Speakers, The Bronze Mortar, (Columbia University College of Pharmacy) June 1957. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Viewpoint Marketing, Newsweek, Sep. 1, 1958, p.37. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - American Cancer Society Advertisement. NY Times Magazine. Mar. 27, 1960. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Press Release: Warner-Lambert and 3M Co. merger possible. Aug. 17, 1960. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Opportunity Still Knocks. Horatio Alger Awards Publication, 1965. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Bobst Dedication, Hahnemann Alumni News, Fall, 1967. p1. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Warner-Lambert, the buy it" Company," Television Age, Nov. 7, 1967. p.21. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - And Co-starring Pat Nixon, NY Times Magazine, Sep. 11, 1970. p.27. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Nixon's 36 Best Friends, Washingtonian, Dec. 1970 p.62. (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Hester, James. New York University, the Urban University Coming of Age. (Newcomen Address, 1970) NY: Newcomen Society, 1971., 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Nixon's Inner Circle of Businessmen, Business Week, Jul. 31, 1971. p.52 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - How Splendid the Day, biography of Elmer Holmes Bobst by Robert Alberts. Publisher's announcement. New York University Press Fall Catalogue, 1971. p.76. (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Nixon's Private Circle, U.S. News and World Report, May 7, 1973. p.25. (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Faster! Faster! - Elmer Bobst, Palm Beach Life. Aug. 1973 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Top 20 Addresses [in New York], Town and Country. Sep. 1973 p.40. (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Annals of Law, The New Yorker, Apr. 17, 1989, p.90. (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University. (Clippings, guest lists, programs, etc.) Oct.-Dec. 1972 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Gala Bobst Library Open House. (Invitations, clippings, brochures, correspondence, etc.) Oct. 1973 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Address: In honor of Dr. Barell. Basel, Feb. 15, 1936. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Address: Hoffmann-La Roche 25th Anniversary, 1936. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Address: Roche Employees, 1942. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Address: Roche Employees, 1946. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Address: Federal Reserve Bank Savings Bond Dinner, 1946. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Address: Security Loan Campaign Dinner, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Address: Lititz High School Alumni, June 1948. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Address: American Pharmaceutical Manufacturers, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Address: Connecticut Cancer Society Campaign Dinner, 1949. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Address: U.S. Savings Bonds, New Jersey Division, 1949. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Address: Lititz High School Alumni, 1951. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Address: The Warner-Hudnut Story, 1952. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Address: Advertising Women's Club of New York, 1952. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Address: "The Realshav Razor" Introduction, 1953. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Address: Lititz, PA. High School Ground-breaking, 1955. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Address. Fairleigh Dickenson College, 1955. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Address: On achieving life membership in the Canadian Foundation for the Advancement of Pharmacy, 1960. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Address: Dedication of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Institute of Clinical Research, 1967. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Article: "Detailing." Druggists Circular, Oct. 1934 p.16. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Article: "His Biggest Fee." Offprint of an editorial from the Roche Review. 1939 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Article: Three Tales Told of Your Doctor, 1941. Reprinted from Roche Review. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Article: "Acorns and Oaks," 1943. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Article: Introduction to Standard Bearers, Jan. 1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Article: "Dear Doctor / Dear Nurse" Letters, 1939-1946. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Article: Introduction to Omnis Orbis Warner, 1949. (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Article: Untitled (on Narcotics 1949). (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Article: "The Sale I Never Forgot," in Printer's Ink, 1954. (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Article: Introduction to 50 Years of Progress, 1928-1978. Hoffman-LaRoche, 1978. (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Article: "The Lure of the Land of Bimini," "Maiden Voyage of Alisa III," "A New Company is Born.", undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Letters: To Dr. Barell. [Memoranda no.18-23, discussing Roche, Inc.] 1941. (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Letters: To Mr. Handsman. (2 tls.) 1941, 1944. (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Letter: "An Oscar to Mr. Bobst!" Letter to U.S. physicians in Medical Marketing, Dec. 1946 pg. 4. (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Letter: "On Medical Writing." M.D. Medical News Magazine, Mar. 1958 p.18. (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Report: Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. 1957 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Unpublished: "A Legacy." [Housed with "Life is What You Make It," an autograph manuscript dated "May 3, 81."], undated (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Unpublished. Biographical data. n.d., undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - The death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Newspaper clippings. Photocopy. 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - The death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. Newspaper clippings. Originals. 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - The Death of Elmer Holmes Bobst. News release. August, 1978. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Program for Burial Service. August 4, 1978. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service for Elmer Holmes Bobst. Invitations and program. Sept. 13, 1978. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Service speech by Lane W. Adams, Sept. 13, 1978. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Service. Invitations list. Sept. 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Service correspondence., undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Service list of attendees., undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - A - H. Letters of Condolence on the Death of Elmer Holmes Bobst., 1978 (Box 34)
  - I - Q. Letters of Condolence. Continuation., 1978 (Box 35)
  - R - Z. Letters of Condolence. Continuation., 1978 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Isaac Walton Bobst. 5 als. 1906, 1908. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 3 als. 1904 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 12 als. 1907 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. 7 als. 1908, 1910, 1920. 1 als. 1920 [photocopy, 1920. EHB to AHB], 1908-1920 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Alice Holmes Bobst. An anthology of verse, Pictures of Memory, annotated by his mother for Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1912 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Bobst Family Members. 6 als. 1906-1908. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Ethel Rose Bobst and Elmer Holmes Bobst. 14 als. 1907 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Ethel Rose Bobst and Elmer Holmes Bobst. 8 als. 1908, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: High School Commencement Announcement. 1901 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Pennsylvania State Pharmaceutical Examining Board. 1906 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1901-1910: Pennsylvania State Board of Law Examiners. Admission to preliminary Bar exam. 1907, 1906-1908 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Political and Business Correspondence. 1940-1971. Hoffman-LaRoche. 1940-1944. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: U.S. Treasury Department. 1943-1944. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Fundraising Correspondence. 1943-1971. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Alfred T. Fuchs. 1946-1947 (Basle, Switzerland) (Box 38, Folder 4.1)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Warner-Hudnut. 1952-1954. (Box 38, Folder 4.2)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Warner/Chilcott. 1958 (Box 38, Folder 4.3)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President and Mrs. Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952-1954. [Includes letters from Press Secretary James Hagerty.] (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Alfred E. Driscoll, Governor of New Jersey. 1956 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Barnard M. Baruch. 1957, 1959. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President Richard M. Nixon. 1958-1971. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: President John F. Kennedy from Elmer Holmes Bobst. 1963 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Robert H. Finch, Secretary of HEW. 1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: John N. Mitchell, Attorney General. 1969 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: William P. Rogers, Secretary of State. 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: John Tower, Senator. 1970 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Donald Schanche. 1971 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Political and Business Correspondence: Social Invitations. 1969-1973. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst to Leah Bobst. 18als. 1862-1864, 1868, n.d., 1862-1868 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Spoon used by Isaac W. Bobst while a Prisoner of War at Andersonville Prison. U.S. Civil War., 1864-1865 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst's Discharge from the Union Army, 1865., undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Isaac W. Bobst In Memoriam. 1924 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Joseph Holmes and Scotia Panner. Marriage License. 1851, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Isaac W. Bobst Correspondence and Family Memorabilia. Caroline M. Cox. Commonplace Book. 1859, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Report. January, 1957. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Pharmaceutical Education Symposium. Papers. January, 1957. (Box 40, Folder 2-8.)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Dinner in Honor of Elmer H. Bobst. June 1957. (Box 40, Folder 9-10.)
  - Bobst-Columbia Plan for Pharmaceutical Education. Wood, David A. Memoir: Elmer H. Bobst: A Man of the Century. November 1989. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Later documents from Mahmoud Bobst, 1974-1993 (Box 41, Folder 1-31)
- Series V: Film, Audio and Video Tape, Slides and Recordings.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  Series V consists of audiovisual materials from Bobst's personal and professional life.
  - Film, 16mm. Home Movies, 1925-1949; cuid005510 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21421 (Box Shared Fales 061, Reel cuid21421)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: 16mm film
    - [Torn Canada], 1933; cuid21422 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1927-08; cuid21423 (Box 42)
    - [39179/EC2 Original], undated; cuid21424 (Box 42)
      Format: 8mm film
    - [unknown], 1928; cuid21425 (Box 42)
    - [From: American Cancer Society], 1948; cuid21426 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1937-07; cuid21427 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1928-07; cuid21428 (Box 42)
    - [from U.W. Vance Hoffmann-LaRoche], 1936-05; cuid21429 (Box 42)
    - [Hoffmann-LaRoche], 1942-05-04; cuid21430 (Box 42)
    - [Bimini], 1949-02; cuid21431 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1936-05; cuid21432 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21433 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1948-02-22; cuid21434 (Box 42)
    - [Diver (Alex) at Havana Harbor, Key West], 1948-02-19-1948-02-20; cuid21435 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21436 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], 1927-08; cuid21437 (Box 42)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21438 (Box 42)
    - [Browns Jaú Trip], undated; cuid21439 (Box 42)
    - [From: American Cancer Society], 1948; cuid21440 (Box 42)
    - [Super SS], 1933-04; cuid21441 (Box 42)
  - Film, 16mm. Home Movies, 1950-1959; cuid21393 (Box 43, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss067_cuid21393)
    16mm film, 400 ft, Black and White, Silent, Preservation note: "Dupe reversal negative."
  - Bobst Family Footage, 1950-1959; cuid21452; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) Master; 1 videocassettes (vhs) Dub (Box 43, Cassette cuid21452A, cuid21452B)
    Telecine transfers of the Bobst family films in the collection.
    Preservation note: The original 16mm films were scanned and are available as digitial access copies.
  - Film, 16mm. Newsreels, 1939-1944; cuid21394 (Box 43)
    - [News Parade: News of Year 1939], cuid21453 (Box 43)
      Housing annotation: sound
    - [News Parade: News of Year 1940], cuid21454 (Box 43)
    - [News Parade: News Parade 1941], cuid21455 (Box 43)
    - [News Parade: War in Europe], undated; cuid21456 (Box 43)
    - [World Parade: America], undated; cuid21457 (Box 43)
    - [News Thrills of 1941, v.2], cuid21458 (Box 43)
  - Film, 16mm. Fit and Fair #35, sponsored by Richard Hudnut, undated; cuid21395 (Box 43)
    Format: 16mm film, Runtime: 18 minutes
    Housing annotation: "Films for Industry, 18:00 rt"
  - Audio Reel. Recorded May 12, 1971. [3 reels], cuid21397 (Box 44)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio
  - Audio Reel. Dedication Ceremony, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University. [3 reels, 2 copies each], 1972-12-16; cuid21398 (Box 44)
  - Bob Hope Promo, undated; cuid21399 (Box 44)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Service, 1978; cuid21400 (Box 44, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss067_cuid21400)
    The memorial takes place in the Elmer C. Bobst Library at New York University. Speakers include Richard Nixon, Lawrence Rockefeller, John Brademas. Mamdouha "Dodo" Bobst is also present.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 55 min.
  - Amer Cancer Society. Million Club, undated; cuid21402 (Box 44, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss067_cuid21402)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 30 min.
  - Unmarked 16 mm open reel films (10), undated; cuid21417 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21442 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21443 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21444 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21445 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21446 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21447 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21448 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21449 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21450 (Box 44)
    - [unknown], undated; cuid21451 (Box 44)
  - [Mr. Bobst], undated; cuid21418 (Box 44)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio
  - American Cancer Society Kick-off Show. [Elmer Holmes Bobst, Bob Hope, Frank Sinatra,et al.], 1947; cuid21403 (Box 45)
    Format: Audio cassette
  - Cancer Drive. [Elmer Holmes Bobst], 1948; cuid21404 (Box 45)
  - International Association of Gerontology. [Elmer Holmes Bobst], 1951; cuid21405 (Box 45)
  - American Cancer Society. [Elmer Holmes Bobst] 1953., cuid21406 (Box 45)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Interview with H. Manning, Station CKGM, Montreal., 1960; cuid21407 (Box 45)
  - Gallatin Award, New York University. Part 1., 1966; cuid21408 (Box 45)
  - Gallatin Award. Part 2., 1966; cuid21409 (Box 45)
  - Hahneman Medical College and Hospital Dedication. Part 1., undated; cuid21410 (Box 45)
  - Hahneman Medical College and Hospital Dedication. Part 2., undated; cuid21411 (Box 45)
  - Dr. Norman Vincent Peale, undated; cuid21396 (Box 45, Audiocassette cuid21396_a, Audiocassette cuid21396_b)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Various Public Addresses by Elmer Holmes Bobst. Side A. (1) Henry Morgan Show. Cancer Appeal. 1948 (2) Special American Show. 1950 (3) American Cancer Society. n.d. (4) "Cancer Control in America". U.S. State Dept. O.I.C. Side B. (1) "You and Medicine." CBS. 1951 (2) Pharmacy Week Program. 1947 (3) Elmer Holmes Bobst Talk on Mutual Broadcasting. 1947, 1947-1951; cuid21412 (Box 45)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Christmas Messages. Side A. Greetings from Elmer Holmes Bobst, Side B. Mendelssohn. Musical Selections., 1950-1956; cuid21413 (Box 45)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. Presenting Personal Philosophies of Thoughtful People. Interviews by Edward R. Murrow. [Elmer Holmes Bobst et al.], undated; cuid21414 (Box 45)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. If I'm Elected; The Actual Voices of Our Presidents and Their Opponent, 1892-1952; cuid21415 (Box 45)
  - Audio Cassettes of Elmer Holmes Bobst and others. President Richard M. Nixon. Inaugural Ceremonies., 1969; cuid21416 (Box 45)
  - Slides. Dedication Ceremony, Elmer Holmes Bobst Library, New York University; unmarked slides, 1954-1972; cuid21401 (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
  - Christmas Message, 1945-1965; cuid28902 (Box 57)
  - Mr. Bobst's Christmas Message to His Employees, 1953; cuid28903 (Box 57)
  - Mr. Bobst's Christmas Message to His Employees, 1953; cuid28904 (Box 57)
  - Untitled, Undated; cuid28905 (Box 57)
  - You and Medicine, October 12, 1951; cuid28906 (Box 57)